{
    "kind": "Dropdown",
    "questions": [
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct category",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP4M2L7b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "hands",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ship",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "berries",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "meat",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "nuts ",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "feet",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "boots",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "leather",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "kayak",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "canoe",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "coach",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "beans",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "moccasin",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "shoulders",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "tunic",
                    "options": [
                        "Transportation",
                        "Parts of the body",
                        "Clothes",
                        "Food"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Complete the conversation choosing the appropriate adjective from the list",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP4M3L12a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Tennis is very__ here.",
                    "options": [
                        "popular",
                        "interesting",
                        "dangerous",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Kayaking is very",
                    "options": [
                        "difficult",
                        "popular",
                        "exciting",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 2,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Rock climbing is an",
                    "options": [
                        "unusual",
                        "interesting",
                        "boring",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think cooking is",
                    "options": [
                        "interesting",
                        "difficult",
                        "dangerous",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}